We, we Swati Dada, your number.  Hey sir, are you
back?  Why?  I don't feel like staying at home.
Hey, what should I do, friend?  This lever is cheating.
Oho, now your insurance has also expired.
Will you have to pay the hospital expenses
from your own pocket?  He has
no tension.  I have ICICI LBA's Elevate
Health Plan with Research Benefit Add-
ons.  Yes Yes i know.  Last time also you were
admitted for liver treatment only, so
how will you get the claim for the same treatment again?  will get.  Why not get it?
Due to the reset add-on in ICICI Low LBR's Elevate Health Plan, if I get
hospitalized again for the same disease, all
my
treatment expenses will be covered without any waiting period.
Oh, what kind of insurance is this?
Elevate It's Just Like A Magic.